{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853456131","data":{"timestamp":" 947853456131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" ac6e834f-60cb-4df9-b7c4-531be1469dec"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alimletea maji ya kunywa na kumpa muda wa kupumzika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853479158","data":{"timestamp":" 947853479157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853479816","data":{"timestamp":" 947853479815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853480031","data":{"timestamp":" 947853480031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853480584","data":{"timestamp":" 947853480584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853481826","data":{"timestamp":" 947853481824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853482076","data":{"timestamp":" 947853482075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853482855","data":{"timestamp":" 947853482854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853483636","data":{"timestamp":" 947853483635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATIMA"," userResponse":" YATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853483922","data":{"timestamp":" 947853483921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853484411","data":{"timestamp":" 947853484411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853485385","data":{"timestamp":" 947853485384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853487657","data":{"timestamp":" 947853487656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853487670","data":{"timestamp":" 947853487670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853489232","data":{"timestamp":" 947853489231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853490488","data":{"timestamp":" 947853490487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853491717","data":{"timestamp":" 947853491717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853492400","data":{"timestamp":" 947853492400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853493198","data":{"timestamp":" 947853493198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853494502","data":{"timestamp":" 947853494501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853495607","data":{"timestamp":" 947853495606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853497637","data":{"timestamp":" 947853497636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853498913","data":{"timestamp":" 947853498913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853500746","data":{"timestamp":" 947853500746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853503257","data":{"timestamp":" 947853503256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YATIMA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853504477","data":{"timestamp":" 947853504477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YATIMA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853506190","data":{"timestamp":" 947853506189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATIMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853506862","data":{"timestamp":" 947853506862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853507275","data":{"timestamp":" 947853507274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853508460","data":{"timestamp":" 947853508459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853509697","data":{"timestamp":" 947853509697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853511417","data":{"timestamp":" 947853511417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mvulana yatima kwa jina Palinyang."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853511727","data":{"timestamp":" 947853511727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853513344","data":{"timestamp":" 947853513343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853513542","data":{"timestamp":" 947853513541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853513623","data":{"timestamp":" 947853513623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853514504","data":{"timestamp":" 947853514504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIUWAWA"," userResponse":" WALIUWAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853514732","data":{"timestamp":" 947853514731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853514771","data":{"timestamp":" 947853514771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKORA"," userResponse":" WAKORA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853515534","data":{"timestamp":" 947853515533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853515881","data":{"timestamp":" 947853515880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853516237","data":{"timestamp":" 947853516236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853516549","data":{"timestamp":" 947853516549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANGA"," userResponse":" MCHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853516820","data":{"timestamp":" 947853516819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853517079","data":{"timestamp":" 947853517078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEZI"," userResponse":" MIEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853517349","data":{"timestamp":" 947853517348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853523339","data":{"timestamp":" 947853523339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853523719","data":{"timestamp":" 947853523719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853524724","data":{"timestamp":" 947853524723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853526650","data":{"timestamp":" 947853526650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" START_PALINYANG"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853528340","data":{"timestamp":" 947853528340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853528510","data":{"timestamp":" 947853528510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIUWAWA"," userResponse":" WALIUWAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853528513","data":{"timestamp":" 947853528513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853528517","data":{"timestamp":" 947853528516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKORA"," userResponse":" WAKORA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853531939","data":{"timestamp":" 947853531939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WALIUWAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853533210","data":{"timestamp":" 947853533209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853534932","data":{"timestamp":" 947853534932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853536088","data":{"timestamp":" 947853536088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853537755","data":{"timestamp":" 947853537755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853539472","data":{"timestamp":" 947853539471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853541519","data":{"timestamp":" 947853541519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853543022","data":{"timestamp":" 947853543022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853544469","data":{"timestamp":" 947853544468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANGA"," userResponse":" MCHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853545557","data":{"timestamp":" 947853545557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853547486","data":{"timestamp":" 947853547485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIEZI"," userResponse":" START_MIEZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853549239","data":{"timestamp":" 947853549238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEZI"," userResponse":" MIEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853550269","data":{"timestamp":" 947853550269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853552709","data":{"timestamp":" 947853552708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKIJIJI"," userResponse":" WANAKIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853553927","data":{"timestamp":" 947853553926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWALIA"," userResponse":" WALIWALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853554712","data":{"timestamp":" 947853554712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853554904","data":{"timestamp":" 947853554903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853555914","data":{"timestamp":" 947853555914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853556371","data":{"timestamp":" 947853556370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853557295","data":{"timestamp":" 947853557294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHANGAA"," userResponse":" KUSHANGAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853557858","data":{"timestamp":" 947853557858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" JINSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853558505","data":{"timestamp":" 947853558505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853559082","data":{"timestamp":" 947853559081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853559903","data":{"timestamp":" 947853559903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUWA"," userResponse":" ANGEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853562634","data":{"timestamp":" 947853562634"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKIJIJI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853566297","data":{"timestamp":" 947853566296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKIJIJI"," userResponse":" START_WANAKIJIJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853568407","data":{"timestamp":" 947853568406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKIJIJI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853570060","data":{"timestamp":" 947853570060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWALIA"," userResponse":" START_WALIWALIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853572635","data":{"timestamp":" 947853572635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWALIA"," userResponse":" START_WALIWALIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853574407","data":{"timestamp":" 947853574406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWALIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853575079","data":{"timestamp":" 947853575079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853575088","data":{"timestamp":" 947853575088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853575180","data":{"timestamp":" 947853575180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853576268","data":{"timestamp":" 947853576267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853577919","data":{"timestamp":" 947853577919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853579766","data":{"timestamp":" 947853579766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" YATIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853580530","data":{"timestamp":" 947853580530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853582039","data":{"timestamp":" 947853582039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHANGAA"," userResponse":" KUSHANGAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853583198","data":{"timestamp":" 947853583198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" JINSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853584447","data":{"timestamp":" 947853584447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853585420","data":{"timestamp":" 947853585419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" START_WALIUWAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853586243","data":{"timestamp":" 947853586243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853586847","data":{"timestamp":" 947853586847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanakijiji waliwalia wazazi wa Palinyang' na kushangaa jinsi mtoto huyo angekuwa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEKUWA"," userResponse":" ANGEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853589151","data":{"timestamp":" 947853589151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853589488","data":{"timestamp":" 947853589487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853590455","data":{"timestamp":" 947853590454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZISHI"," userResponse":" MAZISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853591607","data":{"timestamp":" 947853591606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUSAU"," userResponse":" SAUSAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853592619","data":{"timestamp":" 947853592619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUU"," userResponse":" MKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853592744","data":{"timestamp":" 947853592744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853593622","data":{"timestamp":" 947853593621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853594426","data":{"timestamp":" 947853594426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITA"," userResponse":" ALIITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853595316","data":{"timestamp":" 947853595316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853597148","data":{"timestamp":" 947853597148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853597658","data":{"timestamp":" 947853597657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853598036","data":{"timestamp":" 947853598036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZISHI"," userResponse":" MAZISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853599432","data":{"timestamp":" 947853599432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAUSAU"," userResponse":" MKUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853600396","data":{"timestamp":" 947853600395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SAUSAU"," userResponse":" START_SAUSAU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853602001","data":{"timestamp":" 947853602000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUSAU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853603193","data":{"timestamp":" 947853603192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUU"," userResponse":" SAUSAU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853604302","data":{"timestamp":" 947853604301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUU"," userResponse":" MKUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853605402","data":{"timestamp":" 947853605401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853606133","data":{"timestamp":" 947853606133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" MKUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853607288","data":{"timestamp":" 947853607287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853608694","data":{"timestamp":" 947853608693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853610348","data":{"timestamp":" 947853610348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853612115","data":{"timestamp":" 947853612114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853612905","data":{"timestamp":" 947853612905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya mazishi Sausau mkuu wa kijiji aliita mkutano ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853615112","data":{"timestamp":" 947853615111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUSAU"," userResponse":" SAUSAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853616536","data":{"timestamp":" 947853616536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHESHIMIWA"," userResponse":" ALIHESHIMIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853616610","data":{"timestamp":" 947853616610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853618709","data":{"timestamp":" 947853618709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPWA"," userResponse":" KUOGOPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853619379","data":{"timestamp":" 947853619378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853619706","data":{"timestamp":" 947853619706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853620382","data":{"timestamp":" 947853620381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853621172","data":{"timestamp":" 947853621172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" JINSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853621896","data":{"timestamp":" 947853621895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYO"," userResponse":" ALIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853622619","data":{"timestamp":" 947853622618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VALIA"," userResponse":" VALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853623045","data":{"timestamp":" 947853623044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853623876","data":{"timestamp":" 947853623875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONGEA"," userResponse":" KUONGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853625596","data":{"timestamp":" 947853625596"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAUSAU"," userResponse":" START_SAUSAU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853627422","data":{"timestamp":" 947853627422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUSAU"," userResponse":" SAUSAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853629524","data":{"timestamp":" 947853629524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHESHIMIWA"," userResponse":" START_ALIHESHIMIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853630387","data":{"timestamp":" 947853630386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHESHIMIWA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853632540","data":{"timestamp":" 947853632539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHESHIMIWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853633996","data":{"timestamp":" 947853633995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853634534","data":{"timestamp":" 947853634533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853635376","data":{"timestamp":" 947853635375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPWA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853637132","data":{"timestamp":" 947853637131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853638420","data":{"timestamp":" 947853638420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853638431","data":{"timestamp":" 947853638431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853639702","data":{"timestamp":" 947853639702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853640755","data":{"timestamp":" 947853640755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853642578","data":{"timestamp":" 947853642577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853643149","data":{"timestamp":" 947853643148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853644275","data":{"timestamp":" 947853644274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" JINSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853645562","data":{"timestamp":" 947853645562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYO"," userResponse":" ALIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853646787","data":{"timestamp":" 947853646787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VALIA"," userResponse":" START_VALIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853649029","data":{"timestamp":" 947853649029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VALIA"," userResponse":" VALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853649336","data":{"timestamp":" 947853649336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853650742","data":{"timestamp":" 947853650742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUONGEA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853652504","data":{"timestamp":" 947853652504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sausau aliheshimiwa na kuogopwa sana kwa sababu jinsi alivyo valia na kuongea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONGEA"," userResponse":" KUONGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853654399","data":{"timestamp":" 947853654398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853654965","data":{"timestamp":" 947853654964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853655915","data":{"timestamp":" 947853655915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853656718","data":{"timestamp":" 947853656718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853657372","data":{"timestamp":" 947853657371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853658343","data":{"timestamp":" 947853658343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIFIKA"," userResponse":" ZILIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853659146","data":{"timestamp":" 947853659146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853659748","data":{"timestamp":" 947853659748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853661590","data":{"timestamp":" 947853661590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853662115","data":{"timestamp":" 947853662115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853663522","data":{"timestamp":" 947853663521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853665388","data":{"timestamp":" 947853665387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853667090","data":{"timestamp":" 947853667089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853668715","data":{"timestamp":" 947853668714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853669682","data":{"timestamp":" 947853669681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIFIKA"," userResponse":" START_ZILIFIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853670781","data":{"timestamp":" 947853670781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIFIKA"," userResponse":" KUONGEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853672372","data":{"timestamp":" 947853672372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIFIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853673527","data":{"timestamp":" 947853673527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853674569","data":{"timestamp":" 947853674569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853676237","data":{"timestamp":" 947853676236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853677610","data":{"timestamp":" 947853677610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853678647","data":{"timestamp":" 947853678647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nywele zake zilikuwa ndefu na zilifika mgongoni mwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853681315","data":{"timestamp":" 947853681314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAMINIKA"," userResponse":" ILIAMINIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853681527","data":{"timestamp":" 947853681527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853682074","data":{"timestamp":" 947853682073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853682886","data":{"timestamp":" 947853682885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUSAU"," userResponse":" SAUSAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853683894","data":{"timestamp":" 947853683894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853684943","data":{"timestamp":" 947853684943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853685746","data":{"timestamp":" 947853685746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853685973","data":{"timestamp":" 947853685973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853686482","data":{"timestamp":" 947853686482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853687261","data":{"timestamp":" 947853687261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKATWA"," userResponse":" KUKATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853687505","data":{"timestamp":" 947853687504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853688046","data":{"timestamp":" 947853688045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853688946","data":{"timestamp":" 947853688945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJENGWA"," userResponse":" KUJENGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853692705","data":{"timestamp":" 947853692705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAMINIKA"," userResponse":" START_ILIAMINIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853694948","data":{"timestamp":" 947853694947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAMINIKA"," userResponse":" START_ILIAMINIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853696838","data":{"timestamp":" 947853696837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAMINIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853697729","data":{"timestamp":" 947853697729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853699104","data":{"timestamp":" 947853699104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853700125","data":{"timestamp":" 947853700125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853700875","data":{"timestamp":" 947853700875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAUSAU"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853702254","data":{"timestamp":" 947853702254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUSAU"," userResponse":" SAUSAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853703583","data":{"timestamp":" 947853703583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853705575","data":{"timestamp":" 947853705575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITUNI"," userResponse":" MSITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853706680","data":{"timestamp":" 947853706680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853707776","data":{"timestamp":" 947853707776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853708495","data":{"timestamp":" 947853708495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853710499","data":{"timestamp":" 947853710499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKATWA"," userResponse":" KUKATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853711395","data":{"timestamp":" 947853711395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853712475","data":{"timestamp":" 947853712475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853713167","data":{"timestamp":" 947853713167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUJENGWA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853714273","data":{"timestamp":" 947853714272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iliaminika ya kwamba Sausau aliishi msituni kabla ya miti kukatwa na nyumba kujengwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJENGWA"," userResponse":" KUJENGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853716803","data":{"timestamp":" 947853716802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853717062","data":{"timestamp":" 947853717061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853718091","data":{"timestamp":" 947853718087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853719677","data":{"timestamp":" 947853719676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOKEYOKONI"," userResponse":" LOKEYOKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853720447","data":{"timestamp":" 947853720445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853721148","data":{"timestamp":" 947853721148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853722098","data":{"timestamp":" 947853722098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853722616","data":{"timestamp":" 947853722615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUMO"," userResponse":" HUMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853724433","data":{"timestamp":" 947853724433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853725313","data":{"timestamp":" 947853725313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853726023","data":{"timestamp":" 947853726023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853726615","data":{"timestamp":" 947853726614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853727135","data":{"timestamp":" 947853727134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853730063","data":{"timestamp":" 947853730063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853730370","data":{"timestamp":" 947853730369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853731250","data":{"timestamp":" 947853731249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853732955","data":{"timestamp":" 947853732955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853735235","data":{"timestamp":" 947853735235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LOKEYOKONI"," userResponse":" START_LOKEYOKONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853737702","data":{"timestamp":" 947853737702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LOKEYOKONI"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853739716","data":{"timestamp":" 947853739715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOKEYOKONI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853741573","data":{"timestamp":" 947853741573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" START_TAJIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853743062","data":{"timestamp":" 947853743062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJIRI"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853744336","data":{"timestamp":" 947853744336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853745196","data":{"timestamp":" 947853745195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" START_KIJIJINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853749666","data":{"timestamp":" 947853749665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853750944","data":{"timestamp":" 947853750943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUMO"," userResponse":" HUMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853751776","data":{"timestamp":" 947853751775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853754373","data":{"timestamp":" 947853754373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853756307","data":{"timestamp":" 947853756306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMCHUKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853758010","data":{"timestamp":" 947853758009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853759731","data":{"timestamp":" 947853759731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853761441","data":{"timestamp":" 947853761440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853762400","data":{"timestamp":" 947853762400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853763089","data":{"timestamp":" 947853763089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853763324","data":{"timestamp":" 947853763324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853764930","data":{"timestamp":" 947853764929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati wa mkutano Lokeyokoni tajiri mkubwa kijijini humo alimchukuwa Palinyang' kama mtoto wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853767357","data":{"timestamp":" 947853767356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOKEYOKONI"," userResponse":" LOKEYOKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853768288","data":{"timestamp":" 947853768288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853768539","data":{"timestamp":" 947853768539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853769288","data":{"timestamp":" 947853769287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853769524","data":{"timestamp":" 947853769523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853770207","data":{"timestamp":" 947853770207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKE"," userResponse":" KIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853770727","data":{"timestamp":" 947853770726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853770912","data":{"timestamp":" 947853770911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853771644","data":{"timestamp":" 947853771643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIUME"," userResponse":" KIUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853772538","data":{"timestamp":" 947853772538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853774172","data":{"timestamp":" 947853774171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LOKEYOKONI"," userResponse":" START_LOKEYOKONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853775911","data":{"timestamp":" 947853775911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LOKEYOKONI"," userResponse":" KIKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853777879","data":{"timestamp":" 947853777878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOKEYOKONI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853779480","data":{"timestamp":" 947853779480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" KIUME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853780960","data":{"timestamp":" 947853780959"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853781997","data":{"timestamp":" 947853781997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853782373","data":{"timestamp":" 947853782373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853783549","data":{"timestamp":" 947853783549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853784806","data":{"timestamp":" 947853784805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKE"," userResponse":" KIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853785058","data":{"timestamp":" 947853785058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853785690","data":{"timestamp":" 947853785689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853786082","data":{"timestamp":" 947853786082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIUME"," userResponse":" KIUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853787269","data":{"timestamp":" 947853787268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853789289","data":{"timestamp":" 947853789288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853789516","data":{"timestamp":" 947853789516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853790116","data":{"timestamp":" 947853790116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKE"," userResponse":" KIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853791378","data":{"timestamp":" 947853791377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISAIDIA"," userResponse":" WALISAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853791941","data":{"timestamp":" 947853791940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853792416","data":{"timestamp":" 947853792416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853793359","data":{"timestamp":" 947853793358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853794143","data":{"timestamp":" 947853794142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853794412","data":{"timestamp":" 947853794411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853795504","data":{"timestamp":" 947853795504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853795915","data":{"timestamp":" 947853795914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853796655","data":{"timestamp":" 947853796654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853796844","data":{"timestamp":" 947853796844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853797640","data":{"timestamp":" 947853797639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIUME"," userResponse":" KIUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853798832","data":{"timestamp":" 947853798832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853799640","data":{"timestamp":" 947853799638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUNGA"," userResponse":" KUCHUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853800442","data":{"timestamp":" 947853800441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIFUGO"," userResponse":" MIFUGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853800667","data":{"timestamp":" 947853800666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853801110","data":{"timestamp":" 947853801110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853801615","data":{"timestamp":" 947853801614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853804191","data":{"timestamp":" 947853804191"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853804577","data":{"timestamp":" 947853804577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853805694","data":{"timestamp":" 947853805694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKE"," userResponse":" KIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853807570","data":{"timestamp":" 947853807570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALISAIDIA"," userResponse":" START_WALISAIDIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853809091","data":{"timestamp":" 947853809091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALISAIDIA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853810948","data":{"timestamp":" 947853810948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISAIDIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853812231","data":{"timestamp":" 947853812230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853812312","data":{"timestamp":" 947853812312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853813203","data":{"timestamp":" 947853813203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853814289","data":{"timestamp":" 947853814289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853815338","data":{"timestamp":" 947853815338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853815715","data":{"timestamp":" 947853815714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" START_NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853817014","data":{"timestamp":" 947853817014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853818719","data":{"timestamp":" 947853818719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853819608","data":{"timestamp":" 947853819608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853820758","data":{"timestamp":" 947853820758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853822539","data":{"timestamp":" 947853822539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TAJIRI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853824254","data":{"timestamp":" 947853824253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853825410","data":{"timestamp":" 947853825409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853827339","data":{"timestamp":" 947853827338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853829604","data":{"timestamp":" 947853829604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIUME"," userResponse":" START_KIUME"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853831765","data":{"timestamp":" 947853831765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIUME"," userResponse":" KIUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853835140","data":{"timestamp":" 947853835139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853836367","data":{"timestamp":" 947853836367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853837458","data":{"timestamp":" 947853837458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUNGA"," userResponse":" KUCHUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853838978","data":{"timestamp":" 947853838978"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIFUGO"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853839997","data":{"timestamp":" 947853839996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIFUGO"," userResponse":" MIFUGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853840477","data":{"timestamp":" 947853840477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853841475","data":{"timestamp":" 947853841475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853842094","data":{"timestamp":" 947853842094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa kike walisaidia mama yao kwa kazi za nyumbani na watoto wa kiume walienda kuchunga mifugo ya baba yao."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853844760","data":{"timestamp":" 947853844759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PLINYANG"," userResponse":" PLINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853845862","data":{"timestamp":" 947853845862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853846305","data":{"timestamp":" 947853846305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853847248","data":{"timestamp":" 947853847248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853847916","data":{"timestamp":" 947853847915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853848362","data":{"timestamp":" 947853848361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853848858","data":{"timestamp":" 947853848858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853849662","data":{"timestamp":" 947853849662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBW"," userResponse":" MKUBW"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853850321","data":{"timestamp":" 947853850320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853851062","data":{"timestamp":" 947853851061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853851529","data":{"timestamp":" 947853851529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853852343","data":{"timestamp":" 947853852342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853861815","data":{"timestamp":" 947853861814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PLINYANG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853863989","data":{"timestamp":" 947853863988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853865394","data":{"timestamp":" 947853865394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853867296","data":{"timestamp":" 947853867296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853868306","data":{"timestamp":" 947853868305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853869194","data":{"timestamp":" 947853869193"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853870900","data":{"timestamp":" 947853870900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853872697","data":{"timestamp":" 947853872696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBW"," userResponse":" MKUBW"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853873783","data":{"timestamp":" 947853873783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853875330","data":{"timestamp":" 947853875330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853876589","data":{"timestamp":" 947853876588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853878205","data":{"timestamp":" 947853878204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Plinyang' aliishi kwa familia hii na kuwa mkubw na alikuwa mwenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853880846","data":{"timestamp":" 947853880845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipendwa na alipenda kila mtu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDWA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853881460","data":{"timestamp":" 947853881459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipendwa na alipenda kila mtu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853882406","data":{"timestamp":" 947853882405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipendwa na alipenda kila mtu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853883165","data":{"timestamp":" 947853883164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipendwa na alipenda kila mtu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853883661","data":{"timestamp":" 947853883661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipendwa na alipenda kila mtu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853886237","data":{"timestamp":" 947853886236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipendwa na alipenda kila mtu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDWA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853887125","data":{"timestamp":" 947853887124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipendwa na alipenda kila mtu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853888556","data":{"timestamp":" 947853888556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipendwa na alipenda kila mtu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853890436","data":{"timestamp":" 947853890435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipendwa na alipenda kila mtu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853891674","data":{"timestamp":" 947853891673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipendwa na alipenda kila mtu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853893924","data":{"timestamp":" 947853893922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853894957","data":{"timestamp":" 947853894956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853895746","data":{"timestamp":" 947853895745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853896878","data":{"timestamp":" 947853896877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" MALISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853897329","data":{"timestamp":" 947853897327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853898409","data":{"timestamp":" 947853898408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWACHUNGA"," userResponse":" KUWACHUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853902964","data":{"timestamp":" 947853902964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853904226","data":{"timestamp":" 947853904226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853905835","data":{"timestamp":" 947853905834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPENDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853906394","data":{"timestamp":" 947853906394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUPELEKA"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853908600","data":{"timestamp":" 947853908600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853909774","data":{"timestamp":" 947853909774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853910929","data":{"timestamp":" 947853910929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" START_MALISHONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853912808","data":{"timestamp":" 947853912808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" MALISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853913570","data":{"timestamp":" 947853913569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853915209","data":{"timestamp":" 947853915209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWACHUNGA"," userResponse":" MKUBW"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853918877","data":{"timestamp":" 947853918876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipenda kupeleka wanyama malishoni na kuwachunga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWACHUNGA"," userResponse":" KUWACHUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853921556","data":{"timestamp":" 947853921555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853922831","data":{"timestamp":" 947853922830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853923420","data":{"timestamp":" 947853923419"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853923439","data":{"timestamp":" 947853923439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853924046","data":{"timestamp":" 947853924045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853924700","data":{"timestamp":" 947853924700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853925431","data":{"timestamp":" 947853925430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853926051","data":{"timestamp":" 947853926050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPA"," userResponse":" KUMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853926551","data":{"timestamp":" 947853926550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853927614","data":{"timestamp":" 947853927613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" ALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853931866","data":{"timestamp":" 947853931866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853932879","data":{"timestamp":" 947853932879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPENDA"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853934207","data":{"timestamp":" 947853934206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPENDA"," userResponse":" ALIMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853937006","data":{"timestamp":" 947853937006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853937020","data":{"timestamp":" 947853937020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853937040","data":{"timestamp":" 947853937039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853937403","data":{"timestamp":" 947853937402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853941211","data":{"timestamp":" 947853941210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" START_HATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853941942","data":{"timestamp":" 947853941942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853942374","data":{"timestamp":" 947853942374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853944687","data":{"timestamp":" 947853944687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPA"," userResponse":" KUMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853945076","data":{"timestamp":" 947853945076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853946905","data":{"timestamp":" 947853946905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853947753","data":{"timestamp":" 947853947753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" START_ALINYANG"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853949791","data":{"timestamp":" 947853949791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alimpenda ng'ombe mmoja sana hata kumpa jina Alinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853951847","data":{"timestamp":" 947853951846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" ALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853952661","data":{"timestamp":" 947853952661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853953250","data":{"timestamp":" 947853953250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853953270","data":{"timestamp":" 947853953269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853953963","data":{"timestamp":" 947853953963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853954644","data":{"timestamp":" 947853954643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853955271","data":{"timestamp":" 947853955270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIFUGO"," userResponse":" MIFUGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853955989","data":{"timestamp":" 947853955989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853958145","data":{"timestamp":" 947853958144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" START_ALINYANG"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853959144","data":{"timestamp":" 947853959143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853961132","data":{"timestamp":" 947853961131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853962722","data":{"timestamp":" 947853962722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853962906","data":{"timestamp":" 947853962906"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853964748","data":{"timestamp":" 947853964747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853964916","data":{"timestamp":" 947853964916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853966631","data":{"timestamp":" 947853966631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853968441","data":{"timestamp":" 947853968440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853970950","data":{"timestamp":" 947853970950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIFUGO"," userResponse":" MIFUGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853972264","data":{"timestamp":" 947853972264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853973641","data":{"timestamp":" 947853973640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853974289","data":{"timestamp":" 947853974289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853974966","data":{"timestamp":" 947853974965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853975792","data":{"timestamp":" 947853975792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853976630","data":{"timestamp":" 947853976629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIFUGO"," userResponse":" MIFUGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853977961","data":{"timestamp":" 947853977961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTHAMINI"," userResponse":" ALIMTHAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853978552","data":{"timestamp":" 947853978551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853979011","data":{"timestamp":" 947853979011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853979035","data":{"timestamp":" 947853979034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853979595","data":{"timestamp":" 947853979594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853981405","data":{"timestamp":" 947853981405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853981909","data":{"timestamp":" 947853981908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853982554","data":{"timestamp":" 947853982554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853984087","data":{"timestamp":" 947853984087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853984777","data":{"timestamp":" 947853984776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIFUGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853987957","data":{"timestamp":" 947853987957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIFUGO"," userResponse":" MIFUGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853989084","data":{"timestamp":" 947853989084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTHAMINI"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853991026","data":{"timestamp":" 947853991026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTHAMINI"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853993017","data":{"timestamp":" 947853993016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMTHAMINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853994612","data":{"timestamp":" 947853994611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853995881","data":{"timestamp":" 947853995881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853995886","data":{"timestamp":" 947853995886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853997320","data":{"timestamp":" 947853997319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu hiyo mwenye mifugo alimthamini sana ngo'mbe huyo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947853999690","data":{"timestamp":" 947853999689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854000337","data":{"timestamp":" 947854000337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854001318","data":{"timestamp":" 947854001317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854001980","data":{"timestamp":" 947854001980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIJANA"," userResponse":" VIJANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854002792","data":{"timestamp":" 947854002792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854003715","data":{"timestamp":" 947854003715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHUNGA"," userResponse":" WAKICHUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854004547","data":{"timestamp":" 947854004547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854005900","data":{"timestamp":" 947854005900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIANZA"," userResponse":" KULIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854006975","data":{"timestamp":" 947854006975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYESHA"," userResponse":" KUNYESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854007573","data":{"timestamp":" 947854007572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854008716","data":{"timestamp":" 947854008715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" WALITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854009337","data":{"timestamp":" 947854009336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854009589","data":{"timestamp":" 947854009589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854010699","data":{"timestamp":" 947854010698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIZUIA"," userResponse":" KUJIZUIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854011834","data":{"timestamp":" 947854011834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" MVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854012542","data":{"timestamp":" 947854012541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854012617","data":{"timestamp":" 947854012616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854013242","data":{"timestamp":" 947854013241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854015086","data":{"timestamp":" 947854015085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854016077","data":{"timestamp":" 947854016077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854016196","data":{"timestamp":" 947854016196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854017605","data":{"timestamp":" 947854017604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854018203","data":{"timestamp":" 947854018203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIJANA"," userResponse":" VIJANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854019835","data":{"timestamp":" 947854019835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_WALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854021683","data":{"timestamp":" 947854021683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854024168","data":{"timestamp":" 947854024167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHUNGA"," userResponse":" START_WAKICHUNGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854025411","data":{"timestamp":" 947854025411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHUNGA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854027151","data":{"timestamp":" 947854027150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHUNGA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854029424","data":{"timestamp":" 947854029424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854031466","data":{"timestamp":" 947854031466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854032847","data":{"timestamp":" 947854032846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIANZA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854035205","data":{"timestamp":" 947854035205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULIANZA"," userResponse":" START_KULIANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854036812","data":{"timestamp":" 947854036812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIANZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854037881","data":{"timestamp":" 947854037881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYESHA"," userResponse":" KUNYESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854038991","data":{"timestamp":" 947854038990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KUNYESHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854041220","data":{"timestamp":" 947854041219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854042645","data":{"timestamp":" 947854042645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854044229","data":{"timestamp":" 947854044229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" WALITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854045155","data":{"timestamp":" 947854045154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" WALITAFUTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854045984","data":{"timestamp":" 947854045984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" START_MAHALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854047851","data":{"timestamp":" 947854047851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854048520","data":{"timestamp":" 947854048520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854050338","data":{"timestamp":" 947854050338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIZUIA"," userResponse":" START_KUJIZUIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854051462","data":{"timestamp":" 947854051462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIZUIA"," userResponse":" KUJIZUIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854052688","data":{"timestamp":" 947854052688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854053414","data":{"timestamp":" 947854053414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" MVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854054372","data":{"timestamp":" 947854054371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854055842","data":{"timestamp":" 947854055842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854056645","data":{"timestamp":" 947854056645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja wakati vijana walikuwa wakichunga wanyama kulianza kunyesha na walitafuta mahali pa kujizuia mvua chini ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854058432","data":{"timestamp":" 947854058431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" MVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854059711","data":{"timestamp":" 947854059711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILINYESHA"," userResponse":" ILINYESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854060038","data":{"timestamp":" 947854060038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854060656","data":{"timestamp":" 947854060655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854061755","data":{"timestamp":" 947854061754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854062609","data":{"timestamp":" 947854062609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854063397","data":{"timestamp":" 947854063397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854064214","data":{"timestamp":" 947854064214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854065930","data":{"timestamp":" 947854065929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" MVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854066828","data":{"timestamp":" 947854066828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILINYESHA"," userResponse":" ILINYESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854067776","data":{"timestamp":" 947854067775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854068371","data":{"timestamp":" 947854068371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854069604","data":{"timestamp":" 947854069604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854070215","data":{"timestamp":" 947854070214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" START_HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854071889","data":{"timestamp":" 947854071889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854073778","data":{"timestamp":" 947854073778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854075478","data":{"timestamp":" 947854075478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mvua ilinyesha kwa saa nyingi hadi kulikuwa usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854077398","data":{"timestamp":" 947854077397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854077952","data":{"timestamp":" 947854077952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" MVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854078799","data":{"timestamp":" 947854078798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIACHA"," userResponse":" ILIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854079669","data":{"timestamp":" 947854079668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYESHA"," userResponse":" KUNYESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854081018","data":{"timestamp":" 947854081017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854081964","data":{"timestamp":" 947854081963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854083028","data":{"timestamp":" 947854083028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWACHUKUA"," userResponse":" KUWACHUKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854083782","data":{"timestamp":" 947854083780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854084683","data":{"timestamp":" 947854084682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854085848","data":{"timestamp":" 947854085847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854086690","data":{"timestamp":" 947854086689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854087567","data":{"timestamp":" 947854087567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854089117","data":{"timestamp":" 947854089116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWAONA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854089832","data":{"timestamp":" 947854089832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854090313","data":{"timestamp":" 947854090313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854092998","data":{"timestamp":" 947854092998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854094890","data":{"timestamp":" 947854094889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854097740","data":{"timestamp":" 947854097740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854099143","data":{"timestamp":" 947854099143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854100747","data":{"timestamp":" 947854100747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIACHA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854101982","data":{"timestamp":" 947854101982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIACHA"," userResponse":" ILINYESHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854103652","data":{"timestamp":" 947854103652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIACHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854104424","data":{"timestamp":" 947854104424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYESHA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854105814","data":{"timestamp":" 947854105814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYESHA"," userResponse":" KUNYESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854106726","data":{"timestamp":" 947854106725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" START_WAVULANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854109596","data":{"timestamp":" 947854109596"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" START_WAVULANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854111273","data":{"timestamp":" 947854111272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854112230","data":{"timestamp":" 947854112230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854113393","data":{"timestamp":" 947854113393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854113914","data":{"timestamp":" 947854113914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWACHUKUA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854115789","data":{"timestamp":" 947854115788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWACHUKUA"," userResponse":" KUWACHUKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854116557","data":{"timestamp":" 947854116557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" VIJANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854117558","data":{"timestamp":" 947854117557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854118664","data":{"timestamp":" 947854118664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854119829","data":{"timestamp":" 947854119829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" START_KUWAPELEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854121102","data":{"timestamp":" 947854121101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" START_KUWAPELEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854122970","data":{"timestamp":" 947854122970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854124562","data":{"timestamp":" 947854124562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854127354","data":{"timestamp":" 947854127354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854128873","data":{"timestamp":" 947854128873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWAONA"," userResponse":" START_HAWAKUWAONA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854130182","data":{"timestamp":" 947854130181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWAONA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854132124","data":{"timestamp":" 947854132123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWAONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854133744","data":{"timestamp":" 947854133744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854135429","data":{"timestamp":" 947854135429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854137189","data":{"timestamp":" 947854137189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854139024","data":{"timestamp":" 947854139023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mvua iliacha kunyesha wavulana walienda kuwachukua wanyama ili kuwapeleka nyumbani lakini hawakuwaona wanyama hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854142216","data":{"timestamp":" 947854142216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHOFIA"," userResponse":" WALIHOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854142742","data":{"timestamp":" 947854142741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILE"," userResponse":" KILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854143108","data":{"timestamp":" 947854143107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854143642","data":{"timestamp":" 947854143642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854145084","data":{"timestamp":" 947854145084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWAFANYIA"," userResponse":" ANGEWAFANYIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854146005","data":{"timestamp":" 947854146004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854146837","data":{"timestamp":" 947854146836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEFIKA"," userResponse":" WANGEFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854147678","data":{"timestamp":" 947854147677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854148218","data":{"timestamp":" 947854148218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854149042","data":{"timestamp":" 947854149041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854149420","data":{"timestamp":" 947854149420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854151976","data":{"timestamp":" 947854151976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHOFIA"," userResponse":" WALIHOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854153362","data":{"timestamp":" 947854153362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILE"," userResponse":" KILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854153796","data":{"timestamp":" 947854153795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" START_NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854155843","data":{"timestamp":" 947854155843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854155857","data":{"timestamp":" 947854155856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854156572","data":{"timestamp":" 947854156572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWAFANYIA"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854157819","data":{"timestamp":" 947854157819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWAFANYIA"," userResponse":" START_ANGEWAFANYIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854159917","data":{"timestamp":" 947854159917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWAFANYIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854161527","data":{"timestamp":" 947854161527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854162830","data":{"timestamp":" 947854162830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854164552","data":{"timestamp":" 947854164552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEFIKA"," userResponse":" START_WANGEFIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854165988","data":{"timestamp":" 947854165988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEFIKA"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854167751","data":{"timestamp":" 947854167750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEFIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854168831","data":{"timestamp":" 947854168830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854169425","data":{"timestamp":" 947854169425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854170232","data":{"timestamp":" 947854170231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854171663","data":{"timestamp":" 947854171663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854173235","data":{"timestamp":" 947854173234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854173713","data":{"timestamp":" 947854173712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihofia kile baba yao angewafanyia kama wangefika nyumbani bila wanyama wao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854176066","data":{"timestamp":" 947854176065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKOSA"," userResponse":" WALIPOKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854177144","data":{"timestamp":" 947854177144"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPATA"," userResponse":" KUWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854177824","data":{"timestamp":" 947854177823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854178318","data":{"timestamp":" 947854178317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854179593","data":{"timestamp":" 947854179589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854180245","data":{"timestamp":" 947854180244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854181259","data":{"timestamp":" 947854181258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" WALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854182174","data":{"timestamp":" 947854182173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854182506","data":{"timestamp":" 947854182505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854183167","data":{"timestamp":" 947854183167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBA"," userResponse":" MJOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854183607","data":{"timestamp":" 947854183606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854184760","data":{"timestamp":" 947854184759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854185394","data":{"timestamp":" 947854185394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854186256","data":{"timestamp":" 947854186256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIENDA"," userResponse":" WAKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854186521","data":{"timestamp":" 947854186520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854187356","data":{"timestamp":" 947854187355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854192943","data":{"timestamp":" 947854192943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKOSA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854194210","data":{"timestamp":" 947854194209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKOSA"," userResponse":" START_SHANGAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854196237","data":{"timestamp":" 947854196237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKOSA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854197627","data":{"timestamp":" 947854197627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPATA"," userResponse":" MJOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854198764","data":{"timestamp":" 947854198764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPATA"," userResponse":" KUWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854200767","data":{"timestamp":" 947854200767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" START_WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854201853","data":{"timestamp":" 947854201852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854203568","data":{"timestamp":" 947854203567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854204846","data":{"timestamp":" 947854204845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854207623","data":{"timestamp":" 947854207622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854209032","data":{"timestamp":" 947854209032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854210472","data":{"timestamp":" 947854210471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" START_WALIAMUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854211972","data":{"timestamp":" 947854211972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854213941","data":{"timestamp":" 947854213941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMUA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854215390","data":{"timestamp":" 947854215389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854216196","data":{"timestamp":" 947854216196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854217558","data":{"timestamp":" 947854217558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854218742","data":{"timestamp":" 947854218742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBA"," userResponse":" MJOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854219549","data":{"timestamp":" 947854219549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854221041","data":{"timestamp":" 947854221041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854222465","data":{"timestamp":" 947854222464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854224156","data":{"timestamp":" 947854224156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIENDA"," userResponse":" WAKIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854226370","data":{"timestamp":" 947854226370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854227587","data":{"timestamp":" 947854227586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokosa kuwapata wanyama hao wavulana wawili waliamua kwenda kwa mjomba wao huku wawili wakienda kwa shangazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854229729","data":{"timestamp":" 947854229729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854230643","data":{"timestamp":" 947854230643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" ALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854231784","data":{"timestamp":" 947854231783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWATAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUWATAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854232423","data":{"timestamp":" 947854232423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854232861","data":{"timestamp":" 947854232861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854233512","data":{"timestamp":" 947854233512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" MPAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854234574","data":{"timestamp":" 947854234573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWAPATE"," userResponse":" AWAPATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854236402","data":{"timestamp":" 947854236402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" START_PALINYANG"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854240933","data":{"timestamp":" 947854240933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" START_PALINYANG"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854242661","data":{"timestamp":" 947854242661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854243925","data":{"timestamp":" 947854243925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMUA"," userResponse":" ALIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854245722","data":{"timestamp":" 947854245722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWATAFUTA"," userResponse":" KUWATAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854247032","data":{"timestamp":" 947854247032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854248128","data":{"timestamp":" 947854248128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854249436","data":{"timestamp":" 947854249436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" MPAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854250912","data":{"timestamp":" 947854250912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWAPATE"," userResponse":" AWAPATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854252987","data":{"timestamp":" 947854252987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854253304","data":{"timestamp":" 947854253304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854254039","data":{"timestamp":" 947854254038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBA"," userResponse":" MJOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854254453","data":{"timestamp":" 947854254452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854255258","data":{"timestamp":" 947854255258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854255482","data":{"timestamp":" 947854255481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854256631","data":{"timestamp":" 947854256630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOREKEA"," userResponse":" KUTOREKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854258517","data":{"timestamp":" 947854258517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854259034","data":{"timestamp":" 947854259034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854259941","data":{"timestamp":" 947854259941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBA"," userResponse":" MJOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854260910","data":{"timestamp":" 947854260910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854261844","data":{"timestamp":" 947854261844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" START_SHANGAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854262906","data":{"timestamp":" 947854262905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854264968","data":{"timestamp":" 947854264967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854266636","data":{"timestamp":" 947854266635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854267517","data":{"timestamp":" 947854267516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854268267","data":{"timestamp":" 947854268266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOREKEA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854269542","data":{"timestamp":" 947854269542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOREKEA"," userResponse":" KILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854271413","data":{"timestamp":" 947854271413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa na mjomba wala shangazi wa kutorekea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOREKEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854272503","data":{"timestamp":" 947854272503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854274010","data":{"timestamp":" 947854274010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854274554","data":{"timestamp":" 947854274554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATA"," userResponse":" ALIFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854275060","data":{"timestamp":" 947854275059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINJIA"," userResponse":" VINJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854275347","data":{"timestamp":" 947854275347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYOTE"," userResponse":" VYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854275737","data":{"timestamp":" 947854275737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOVIJUA"," userResponse":" ALIVYOVIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854276518","data":{"timestamp":" 947854276518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854277136","data":{"timestamp":" 947854277135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" AKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854277424","data":{"timestamp":" 947854277422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854277593","data":{"timestamp":" 947854277592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854277680","data":{"timestamp":" 947854277680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854277893","data":{"timestamp":" 947854277893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854278123","data":{"timestamp":" 947854278122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854278145","data":{"timestamp":" 947854278145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854278409","data":{"timestamp":" 947854278409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMPENDAYE"," userResponse":" AMPENDAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854286864","data":{"timestamp":" 947854286864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854287602","data":{"timestamp":" 947854287601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATA"," userResponse":" AMPENDAYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854289860","data":{"timestamp":" 947854289860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854291795","data":{"timestamp":" 947854291795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854293280","data":{"timestamp":" 947854293279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VINJIA"," userResponse":" ALIFUATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854294605","data":{"timestamp":" 947854294604"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINJIA"," userResponse":" VINJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854295998","data":{"timestamp":" 947854295998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYOTE"," userResponse":" VYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854297797","data":{"timestamp":" 947854297796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOVIJUA"," userResponse":" START_ALIVYOVIJUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854300368","data":{"timestamp":" 947854300368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOVIJUA"," userResponse":" START_ALIVYOVIJUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854302862","data":{"timestamp":" 947854302861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOVIJUA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854304827","data":{"timestamp":" 947854304827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854305640","data":{"timestamp":" 947854305640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" START_AKIIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854307097","data":{"timestamp":" 947854307096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" AKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854307109","data":{"timestamp":" 947854307108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854307167","data":{"timestamp":" 947854307167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854308098","data":{"timestamp":" 947854308098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854308116","data":{"timestamp":" 947854308115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854310426","data":{"timestamp":" 947854310426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854312680","data":{"timestamp":" 947854312680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854312686","data":{"timestamp":" 947854312686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854314770","data":{"timestamp":" 947854314769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMPENDAYE"," userResponse":" START_AMPENDAYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854317099","data":{"timestamp":" 947854317099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMPENDAYE"," userResponse":" START_AMPENDAYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854319003","data":{"timestamp":" 947854319003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' alifuata vinjia vyote alivyovijua huku akiimba wimbo wa jina la ngo'mbe ampendaye."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMPENDAYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854320607","data":{"timestamp":" 947854320607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854321089","data":{"timestamp":" 947854321089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854321522","data":{"timestamp":" 947854321522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854322856","data":{"timestamp":" 947854322855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIVYOENDA"," userResponse":" ULIVYOENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854323956","data":{"timestamp":" 947854323956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIII"," userResponse":" PIII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854324629","data":{"timestamp":" 947854324629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PI"," userResponse":" PI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854325508","data":{"timestamp":" 947854325507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" ALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854327197","data":{"timestamp":" 947854327197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854328265","data":{"timestamp":" 947854328265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854329888","data":{"timestamp":" 947854329888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854331378","data":{"timestamp":" 947854331378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854332230","data":{"timestamp":" 947854332230"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIVYOENDA"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854333646","data":{"timestamp":" 947854333645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIVYOENDA"," userResponse":" ULIVYOENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854334783","data":{"timestamp":" 947854334782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIII"," userResponse":" PIII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854335148","data":{"timestamp":" 947854335147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PI"," userResponse":" PI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854339563","data":{"timestamp":" 947854339563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" ULIVYOENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854341932","data":{"timestamp":" 947854341931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" START_ALINYANG"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854343945","data":{"timestamp":" 947854343945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi ndivyo wimbo ulivyoenda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854345743","data":{"timestamp":" 947854345743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Piii pi Alinyang'!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIII"," userResponse":" PIII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854346378","data":{"timestamp":" 947854346377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Piii pi Alinyang'!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PI"," userResponse":" PI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854347261","data":{"timestamp":" 947854347258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Piii pi Alinyang'!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" ALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854348799","data":{"timestamp":" 947854348799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Piii pi Alinyang'!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIII"," userResponse":" PIII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854349219","data":{"timestamp":" 947854349219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Piii pi Alinyang'!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PI"," userResponse":" PI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854350315","data":{"timestamp":" 947854350315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Piii pi Alinyang'!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854352064","data":{"timestamp":" 947854352064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Piii pi Alinyang'!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" ALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854353828","data":{"timestamp":" 947854353828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chaka akula chi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKA"," userResponse":" CHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854354753","data":{"timestamp":" 947854354752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chaka akula chi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKULA"," userResponse":" AKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854355502","data":{"timestamp":" 947854355501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chaka akula chi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHI"," userResponse":" CHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854357326","data":{"timestamp":" 947854357326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chaka akula chi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKA"," userResponse":" CHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854358219","data":{"timestamp":" 947854358219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chaka akula chi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKULA"," userResponse":" AKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854358821","data":{"timestamp":" 947854358821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chaka akula chi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHI"," userResponse":" CHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854360516","data":{"timestamp":" 947854360515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chaka orete chi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKA"," userResponse":" CHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854361323","data":{"timestamp":" 947854361322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chaka orete chi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ORETE"," userResponse":" ORETE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854362106","data":{"timestamp":" 947854362105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chaka orete chi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHI"," userResponse":" CHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854363843","data":{"timestamp":" 947854363843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chaka orete chi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKA"," userResponse":" CHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854364564","data":{"timestamp":" 947854364563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chaka orete chi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ORETE"," userResponse":" ORETE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854364797","data":{"timestamp":" 947854364796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chaka orete chi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHI"," userResponse":" CHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854367394","data":{"timestamp":" 947854367394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854368466","data":{"timestamp":" 947854368465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDELEA"," userResponse":" ALIENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854369099","data":{"timestamp":" 947854369098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854369565","data":{"timestamp":" 947854369565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854370199","data":{"timestamp":" 947854370198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854370987","data":{"timestamp":" 947854370986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854371532","data":{"timestamp":" 947854371531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854373923","data":{"timestamp":" 947854373922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" ALIENDELEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854375924","data":{"timestamp":" 947854375923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854377911","data":{"timestamp":" 947854377911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIENDELEA"," userResponse":" ALIENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854379320","data":{"timestamp":" 947854379319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854380353","data":{"timestamp":" 947854380353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854381856","data":{"timestamp":" 947854381855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854382745","data":{"timestamp":" 947854382744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854384152","data":{"timestamp":" 947854384152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854385607","data":{"timestamp":" 947854385607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854387007","data":{"timestamp":" 947854387006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854388619","data":{"timestamp":" 947854388618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854389644","data":{"timestamp":" 947854389643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854390746","data":{"timestamp":" 947854390745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palinyang' aliendelea kuimba wimbo huo usiku wote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854393862","data":{"timestamp":" 947854393862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKANYANGA"," userResponse":" ALIKANYANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854394828","data":{"timestamp":" 947854394827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYESI"," userResponse":" KINYESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854395088","data":{"timestamp":" 947854395087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854395606","data":{"timestamp":" 947854395606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854395636","data":{"timestamp":" 947854395635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854396833","data":{"timestamp":" 947854396832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854397697","data":{"timestamp":" 947854397697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854398736","data":{"timestamp":" 947854398735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854401265","data":{"timestamp":" 947854401263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKANYANGA"," userResponse":" START_ALIKANYANGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854403676","data":{"timestamp":" 947854403676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKANYANGA"," userResponse":" ALIKANYANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854405296","data":{"timestamp":" 947854405296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYESI"," userResponse":" KINYESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854406049","data":{"timestamp":" 947854406049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854407378","data":{"timestamp":" 947854407378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854409100","data":{"timestamp":" 947854409099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854410342","data":{"timestamp":" 947854410342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854414212","data":{"timestamp":" 947854414212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854415174","data":{"timestamp":" 947854415174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854417352","data":{"timestamp":" 947854417352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854419362","data":{"timestamp":" 947854419361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854420942","data":{"timestamp":" 947854420942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikanyanga kinyesi cha ngo'mbe lakini kilikuwa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854422704","data":{"timestamp":" 947854422704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854424185","data":{"timestamp":" 947854424185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKANYAGA"," userResponse":" ALIKANYAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854425082","data":{"timestamp":" 947854425081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKOJO"," userResponse":" MKOJO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854425338","data":{"timestamp":" 947854425338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854425844","data":{"timestamp":" 947854425843"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854425866","data":{"timestamp":" 947854425865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854426527","data":{"timestamp":" 947854426526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854426976","data":{"timestamp":" 947854426975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854427909","data":{"timestamp":" 947854427909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854428683","data":{"timestamp":" 947854428682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854429728","data":{"timestamp":" 947854429727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854430514","data":{"timestamp":" 947854430513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854431938","data":{"timestamp":" 947854431937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUKATA"," userResponse":" HAKUKATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854432706","data":{"timestamp":" 947854432704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854433573","data":{"timestamp":" 947854433573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854434304","data":{"timestamp":" 947854434304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854435557","data":{"timestamp":" 947854435557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUMAINI"," userResponse":" MATUMAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854436070","data":{"timestamp":" 947854436070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854437153","data":{"timestamp":" 947854437152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPATA"," userResponse":" KUWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854437667","data":{"timestamp":" 947854437667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854437695","data":{"timestamp":" 947854437695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854438196","data":{"timestamp":" 947854438196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854440186","data":{"timestamp":" 947854440186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854441214","data":{"timestamp":" 947854441214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKANYAGA"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854442089","data":{"timestamp":" 947854442088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKANYAGA"," userResponse":" START_ALIKANYAGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854444137","data":{"timestamp":" 947854444136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKANYAGA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854445020","data":{"timestamp":" 947854445019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKOJO"," userResponse":" MKOJO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854445722","data":{"timestamp":" 947854445722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854445902","data":{"timestamp":" 947854445901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854446200","data":{"timestamp":" 947854446200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854447376","data":{"timestamp":" 947854447376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854449276","data":{"timestamp":" 947854449276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854449991","data":{"timestamp":" 947854449991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854451180","data":{"timestamp":" 947854451180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854453463","data":{"timestamp":" 947854453463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854455464","data":{"timestamp":" 947854455464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854455968","data":{"timestamp":" 947854455968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854458089","data":{"timestamp":" 947854458088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854459078","data":{"timestamp":" 947854459078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854460595","data":{"timestamp":" 947854460595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854462188","data":{"timestamp":" 947854462187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854464161","data":{"timestamp":" 947854464161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUKATA"," userResponse":" HAKUKATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854465265","data":{"timestamp":" 947854465265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854466179","data":{"timestamp":" 947854466178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854468177","data":{"timestamp":" 947854468177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854470066","data":{"timestamp":" 947854470066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUMAINI"," userResponse":" MATUMAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854470790","data":{"timestamp":" 947854470790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854472060","data":{"timestamp":" 947854472060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPATA"," userResponse":" KUWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854472247","data":{"timestamp":" 947854472247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854472758","data":{"timestamp":" 947854472758"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854473692","data":{"timestamp":" 947854473692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha alikanyaga mkojo wa ngo'mbe na pia ulikuwa baridi lakini hivyo hakukata tamaa au kukosa matumaini ya kuwapata ngo'mbe hao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854476131","data":{"timestamp":" 947854476130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854477799","data":{"timestamp":" 947854477799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPOPAMBAZUKA"," userResponse":" KULIPOPAMBAZUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854479136","data":{"timestamp":" 947854479136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854480144","data":{"timestamp":" 947854480143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854481006","data":{"timestamp":" 947854481005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854481836","data":{"timestamp":" 947854481836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854482698","data":{"timestamp":" 947854482696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854483160","data":{"timestamp":" 947854483159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854484131","data":{"timestamp":" 947854484130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPATA"," userResponse":" KUWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854484815","data":{"timestamp":" 947854484815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854485482","data":{"timestamp":" 947854485480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854485642","data":{"timestamp":" 947854485641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854486649","data":{"timestamp":" 947854486648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULINZI"," userResponse":" ULINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854487161","data":{"timestamp":" 947854487161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854488016","data":{"timestamp":" 947854488015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIFU"," userResponse":" CHIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854488151","data":{"timestamp":" 947854488151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854488934","data":{"timestamp":" 947854488934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854489477","data":{"timestamp":" 947854489477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HICHO"," userResponse":" HICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854491947","data":{"timestamp":" 947854491947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854495456","data":{"timestamp":" 947854495456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPOPAMBAZUKA"," userResponse":" START_KULIPOPAMBAZUKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854498013","data":{"timestamp":" 947854498013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPOPAMBAZUKA"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854500169","data":{"timestamp":" 947854500169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPOPAMBAZUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854502054","data":{"timestamp":" 947854502054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854502892","data":{"timestamp":" 947854502891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" START_PALINYANG"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854504576","data":{"timestamp":" 947854504575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854508038","data":{"timestamp":" 947854508038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854509276","data":{"timestamp":" 947854509275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854509673","data":{"timestamp":" 947854509673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854511152","data":{"timestamp":" 947854511152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854511642","data":{"timestamp":" 947854511642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854513164","data":{"timestamp":" 947854513163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPATA"," userResponse":" KUWAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854514671","data":{"timestamp":" 947854514671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854515570","data":{"timestamp":" 947854515569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854515934","data":{"timestamp":" 947854515933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854519749","data":{"timestamp":" 947854519749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULINZI"," userResponse":" ULINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854521132","data":{"timestamp":" 947854521132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854522377","data":{"timestamp":" 947854522377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIFU"," userResponse":" CHIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854522745","data":{"timestamp":" 947854522744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854523637","data":{"timestamp":" 947854523637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854524370","data":{"timestamp":" 947854524369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HICHO"," userResponse":" START_HICHO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854527232","data":{"timestamp":" 947854527232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HICHO"," userResponse":" HICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854529768","data":{"timestamp":" 947854529767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALLIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ALLIMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854530457","data":{"timestamp":" 947854530456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIFU"," userResponse":" CHIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854531082","data":{"timestamp":" 947854531081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854532253","data":{"timestamp":" 947854532252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAACHILIA"," userResponse":" KUWAACHILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854532862","data":{"timestamp":" 947854532861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854532884","data":{"timestamp":" 947854532884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854533510","data":{"timestamp":" 947854533509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854534355","data":{"timestamp":" 947854534354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854535208","data":{"timestamp":" 947854535208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYMBANI"," userResponse":" NYMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854536334","data":{"timestamp":" 947854536334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854537043","data":{"timestamp":" 947854537042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854537626","data":{"timestamp":" 947854537625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIFU"," userResponse":" CHIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854538207","data":{"timestamp":" 947854538206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854539474","data":{"timestamp":" 947854539474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKATAA"," userResponse":" ALIKATAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854542639","data":{"timestamp":" 947854542638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALLIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854545694","data":{"timestamp":" 947854545694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALLIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854547403","data":{"timestamp":" 947854547403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALLIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854547906","data":{"timestamp":" 947854547906"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHIFU"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854548870","data":{"timestamp":" 947854548870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIFU"," userResponse":" CHIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854549335","data":{"timestamp":" 947854549335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854550965","data":{"timestamp":" 947854550965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAACHILIA"," userResponse":" START_WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854552544","data":{"timestamp":" 947854552544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAACHILIA"," userResponse":" START_KUWAACHILIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854554495","data":{"timestamp":" 947854554495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAACHILIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854555647","data":{"timestamp":" 947854555647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854556403","data":{"timestamp":" 947854556403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854556880","data":{"timestamp":" 947854556880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854558748","data":{"timestamp":" 947854558748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854559823","data":{"timestamp":" 947854559823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854561858","data":{"timestamp":" 947854561858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854562668","data":{"timestamp":" 947854562668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854564158","data":{"timestamp":" 947854564158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYMBANI"," userResponse":" NYMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854565326","data":{"timestamp":" 947854565325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854568882","data":{"timestamp":" 947854568882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" START_ALLIMWOMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854570261","data":{"timestamp":" 947854570261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854572072","data":{"timestamp":" 947854572072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHIFU"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854573651","data":{"timestamp":" 947854573650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIFU"," userResponse":" CHIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854575066","data":{"timestamp":" 947854575066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854577076","data":{"timestamp":" 947854577076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Allimwomba chifu huyo kuwaachilia ngo'mbe hao kwenda nymbani naye lakini chifu huyo alikataa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKATAA"," userResponse":" ALIKATAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854579032","data":{"timestamp":" 947854579031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854579820","data":{"timestamp":" 947854579820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKATA"," userResponse":" KUKATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854580720","data":{"timestamp":" 947854580720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854581865","data":{"timestamp":" 947854581864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854582796","data":{"timestamp":" 947854582795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854583529","data":{"timestamp":" 947854583529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854584009","data":{"timestamp":" 947854584009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854584619","data":{"timestamp":" 947854584619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854585678","data":{"timestamp":" 947854585677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUDI"," userResponse":" AKIRUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854586490","data":{"timestamp":" 947854586489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854588411","data":{"timestamp":" 947854588411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854590085","data":{"timestamp":" 947854590084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKATA"," userResponse":" KUKATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854590794","data":{"timestamp":" 947854590793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854592186","data":{"timestamp":" 947854592186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854594101","data":{"timestamp":" 947854594101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854596428","data":{"timestamp":" 947854596427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854598116","data":{"timestamp":" 947854598115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854599607","data":{"timestamp":" 947854599606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854600567","data":{"timestamp":" 947854600567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" START_KUIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854602089","data":{"timestamp":" 947854602089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854603588","data":{"timestamp":" 947854603588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854604368","data":{"timestamp":" 947854604368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" KUKATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854606182","data":{"timestamp":" 947854606182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854607671","data":{"timestamp":" 947854607671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIRUDI"," userResponse":" AKIRUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854608599","data":{"timestamp":" 947854608599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" START_NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854611254","data":{"timestamp":" 947854611254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa kukata tamaa Palinyang' alianza kuimba wimbo wake akirudi nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854612703","data":{"timestamp":" 947854612703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854613234","data":{"timestamp":" 947854613233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854613724","data":{"timestamp":" 947854613724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIPO"," userResponse":" NDIPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854614691","data":{"timestamp":" 947854614690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" ALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854615289","data":{"timestamp":" 947854615288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854615315","data":{"timestamp":" 947854615315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854615938","data":{"timestamp":" 947854615937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854617190","data":{"timestamp":" 947854617189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIMSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854618210","data":{"timestamp":" 947854618210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854619200","data":{"timestamp":" 947854619200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" AKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854621293","data":{"timestamp":" 947854621292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854621824","data":{"timestamp":" 947854621824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854623013","data":{"timestamp":" 947854623012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIPO"," userResponse":" NDIPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854624505","data":{"timestamp":" 947854624505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854625689","data":{"timestamp":" 947854625689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" ALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854626276","data":{"timestamp":" 947854626276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGO"," userResponse":" NGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854627336","data":{"timestamp":" 947854627336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBE"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854630155","data":{"timestamp":" 947854630155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" NDIPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854631835","data":{"timestamp":" 947854631835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854634291","data":{"timestamp":" 947854634290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIMSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854637551","data":{"timestamp":" 947854637551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854640703","data":{"timestamp":" 947854640702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854641812","data":{"timestamp":" 947854641812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" START_AKIIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854649001","data":{"timestamp":" 947854649000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" START_AKIIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854650647","data":{"timestamp":" 947854650646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hapo ndipo Alinyang' ngo'mbe mzee alimsikia Palinyang' akiimba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854651552","data":{"timestamp":" 947854651551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854653237","data":{"timestamp":" 947854653236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" ALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854654133","data":{"timestamp":" 947854654132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEKA"," userResponse":" ALIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854654294","data":{"timestamp":" 947854654294"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854654874","data":{"timestamp":" 947854654873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854655040","data":{"timestamp":" 947854655039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854655494","data":{"timestamp":" 947854655493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854655701","data":{"timestamp":" 947854655700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854656336","data":{"timestamp":" 947854656335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFUATA"," userResponse":" KUMFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854656841","data":{"timestamp":" 947854656841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854664261","data":{"timestamp":" 947854664261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYANG"," userResponse":" ALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854665350","data":{"timestamp":" 947854665350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEKA"," userResponse":" ALIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854666778","data":{"timestamp":" 947854666777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" START_MASIKIO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854668287","data":{"timestamp":" 947854668287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854669887","data":{"timestamp":" 947854669886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854670782","data":{"timestamp":" 947854670782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854671477","data":{"timestamp":" 947854671477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854672044","data":{"timestamp":" 947854672043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854673174","data":{"timestamp":" 947854673174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854674350","data":{"timestamp":" 947854674350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" KUANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854676857","data":{"timestamp":" 947854676857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFUATA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854678637","data":{"timestamp":" 947854678637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFUATA"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854680520","data":{"timestamp":" 947854680520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFUATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854682784","data":{"timestamp":" 947854682784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" KUMFUATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854685367","data":{"timestamp":" 947854685367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" START_PALINYANG"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854687038","data":{"timestamp":" 947854687038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alinyang' aliweka masikio yake juu na kuanza kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854688880","data":{"timestamp":" 947854688880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854689370","data":{"timestamp":" 947854689370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854690247","data":{"timestamp":" 947854690247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITOKA"," userResponse":" WALITOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854691024","data":{"timestamp":" 947854691023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854692943","data":{"timestamp":" 947854692943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854694205","data":{"timestamp":" 947854694205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEFUNGIWA"," userResponse":" WAMEFUNGIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854694578","data":{"timestamp":" 947854694578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854695529","data":{"timestamp":" 947854695529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFUATA"," userResponse":" KUMFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854696481","data":{"timestamp":" 947854696480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854698770","data":{"timestamp":" 947854698770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854699882","data":{"timestamp":" 947854699882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854700864","data":{"timestamp":" 947854700863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALITOKA"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854702601","data":{"timestamp":" 947854702601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALITOKA"," userResponse":" START_WALITOKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854704351","data":{"timestamp":" 947854704350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITOKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854706206","data":{"timestamp":" 947854706205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854707901","data":{"timestamp":" 947854707900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854709331","data":{"timestamp":" 947854709331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854710298","data":{"timestamp":" 947854710298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKOKUWA"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854713156","data":{"timestamp":" 947854713156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_WALIKOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854715017","data":{"timestamp":" 947854715017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854716382","data":{"timestamp":" 947854716382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEFUNGIWA"," userResponse":" WALIKOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854717256","data":{"timestamp":" 947854717256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEFUNGIWA"," userResponse":" START_WAMEFUNGIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854719036","data":{"timestamp":" 947854719036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEFUNGIWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854719199","data":{"timestamp":" 947854719199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854722520","data":{"timestamp":" 947854722520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFUATA"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854726441","data":{"timestamp":" 947854726440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFUATA"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854728336","data":{"timestamp":" 947854728335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFUATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854728625","data":{"timestamp":" 947854728625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854732494","data":{"timestamp":" 947854732494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" MBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854734248","data":{"timestamp":" 947854734247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wote walitoka kule walikokuwa wamefungiwa na kumfuata Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854734793","data":{"timestamp":" 947854734793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwaelekeza wanyama hao nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854737046","data":{"timestamp":" 947854737045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwaelekeza wanyama hao nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854737554","data":{"timestamp":" 947854737554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwaelekeza wanyama hao nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854737699","data":{"timestamp":" 947854737698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwaelekeza wanyama hao nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854738087","data":{"timestamp":" 947854738087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwaelekeza wanyama hao nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854742251","data":{"timestamp":" 947854742251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwaelekeza wanyama hao nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWAELEKEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854742718","data":{"timestamp":" 947854742718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwaelekeza wanyama hao nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854743144","data":{"timestamp":" 947854743143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwaelekeza wanyama hao nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854744237","data":{"timestamp":" 947854744237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliwaelekeza wanyama hao nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854747047","data":{"timestamp":" 947854747047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854748078","data":{"timestamp":" 947854748077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854748790","data":{"timestamp":" 947854748789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854749486","data":{"timestamp":" 947854749485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854750442","data":{"timestamp":" 947854750442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854751779","data":{"timestamp":" 947854751778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWANGONJA"," userResponse":" WAKIWANGONJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854752055","data":{"timestamp":" 947854752055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854752845","data":{"timestamp":" 947854752844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854753600","data":{"timestamp":" 947854753600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854754855","data":{"timestamp":" 947854754854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMESIKIA"," userResponse":" WAMESIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854755729","data":{"timestamp":" 947854755728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854755859","data":{"timestamp":" 947854755859"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854756907","data":{"timestamp":" 947854756907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854758021","data":{"timestamp":" 947854758020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854758362","data":{"timestamp":" 947854758361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854759066","data":{"timestamp":" 947854759066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854766528","data":{"timestamp":" 947854766528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" START_WALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854767591","data":{"timestamp":" 947854767591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854769606","data":{"timestamp":" 947854769605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854770497","data":{"timestamp":" 947854770497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854771276","data":{"timestamp":" 947854771275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854773120","data":{"timestamp":" 947854773120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854773719","data":{"timestamp":" 947854773719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" START_KIJIJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854775936","data":{"timestamp":" 947854775936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854777956","data":{"timestamp":" 947854777956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854778974","data":{"timestamp":" 947854778973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_WALIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854780886","data":{"timestamp":" 947854780886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854781853","data":{"timestamp":" 947854781853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWANGONJA"," userResponse":" START_WAKIWANGONJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854783259","data":{"timestamp":" 947854783259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWANGONJA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854785165","data":{"timestamp":" 947854785165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWANGONJA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854787009","data":{"timestamp":" 947854787009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854787462","data":{"timestamp":" 947854787461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" START_SABABU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854789207","data":{"timestamp":" 947854789206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854791003","data":{"timestamp":" 947854791002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854793752","data":{"timestamp":" 947854793752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" START_MBALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854797773","data":{"timestamp":" 947854797773"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854799801","data":{"timestamp":" 947854799801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAMESIKIA"," userResponse":" START_WAMESIKIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854800840","data":{"timestamp":" 947854800840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAMESIKIA"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854802687","data":{"timestamp":" 947854802687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMESIKIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854804492","data":{"timestamp":" 947854804491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854806660","data":{"timestamp":" 947854806660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854808074","data":{"timestamp":" 947854808074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854810021","data":{"timestamp":" 947854810021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854811718","data":{"timestamp":" 947854811718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854812898","data":{"timestamp":" 947854812898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854815683","data":{"timestamp":" 947854815683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854816195","data":{"timestamp":" 947854816195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854817443","data":{"timestamp":" 947854817442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" START_MBALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854823833","data":{"timestamp":" 947854823832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854825695","data":{"timestamp":" 947854825694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854826640","data":{"timestamp":" 947854826639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIMBA"," userResponse":" WALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854827251","data":{"timestamp":" 947854827250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854827479","data":{"timestamp":" 947854827478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854828417","data":{"timestamp":" 947854828416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSIFU"," userResponse":" KUMSIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854829445","data":{"timestamp":" 947854829445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854831115","data":{"timestamp":" 947854831115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854831854","data":{"timestamp":" 947854831853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIMBA"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854833105","data":{"timestamp":" 947854833105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIMBA"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854834944","data":{"timestamp":" 947854834943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854835912","data":{"timestamp":" 947854835911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" START_NYIMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854836831","data":{"timestamp":" 947854836831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854837232","data":{"timestamp":" 947854837232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854838451","data":{"timestamp":" 947854838450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMSIFU"," userResponse":" KUMSIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854839948","data":{"timestamp":" 947854839948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854842003","data":{"timestamp":" 947854842003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854843685","data":{"timestamp":" 947854843684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote Waliimba nyimbo za kumsifu Palinyang'."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854846257","data":{"timestamp":" 947854846256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOKEYOKONI"," userResponse":" LOKEYOKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854847669","data":{"timestamp":" 947854847668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSHUKURU"," userResponse":" ALIMSHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854848669","data":{"timestamp":" 947854848668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854849271","data":{"timestamp":" 947854849270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854850402","data":{"timestamp":" 947854850402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMNUNULIA"," userResponse":" KUMNUNULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854851101","data":{"timestamp":" 947854851100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKOBA"," userResponse":" MKOBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854852009","data":{"timestamp":" 947854852009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEKUNDU"," userResponse":" MWEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854852689","data":{"timestamp":" 947854852688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854853631","data":{"timestamp":" 947854853631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBEA"," userResponse":" KUBEBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854854600","data":{"timestamp":" 947854854600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" VITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854854738","data":{"timestamp":" 947854854737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854855331","data":{"timestamp":" 947854855330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854858134","data":{"timestamp":" 947854858134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LOKEYOKONI"," userResponse":" MKOBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854859858","data":{"timestamp":" 947854859858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LOKEYOKONI"," userResponse":" MKOBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854861873","data":{"timestamp":" 947854861873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOKEYOKONI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854863922","data":{"timestamp":" 947854863922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSHUKURU"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854866679","data":{"timestamp":" 947854866679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSHUKURU"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854868412","data":{"timestamp":" 947854868411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSHUKURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854872431","data":{"timestamp":" 947854872431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854874415","data":{"timestamp":" 947854874415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" START_PALINYANG"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854876148","data":{"timestamp":" 947854876148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854877934","data":{"timestamp":" 947854877934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854882311","data":{"timestamp":" 947854882311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMNUNULIA"," userResponse":" KUMNUNULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854883620","data":{"timestamp":" 947854883620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKOBA"," userResponse":" MKOBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854885304","data":{"timestamp":" 947854885304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEKUNDU"," userResponse":" MWEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854886024","data":{"timestamp":" 947854886023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854886860","data":{"timestamp":" 947854886860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBEA"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854888558","data":{"timestamp":" 947854888558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBEA"," userResponse":" KUBEBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854889658","data":{"timestamp":" 947854889658"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" START_VITABU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854891360","data":{"timestamp":" 947854891359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" START_VITABU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854892840","data":{"timestamp":" 947854892840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITABU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854893003","data":{"timestamp":" 947854893003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854893148","data":{"timestamp":" 947854893148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lokeyokoni alimshukuru Palinyang' na kumnunulia mkoba mwekundu wa kubebea vitabu vya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854894640","data":{"timestamp":" 947854894639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854895269","data":{"timestamp":" 947854895268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854895778","data":{"timestamp":" 947854895777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854896848","data":{"timestamp":" 947854896847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854897701","data":{"timestamp":" 947854897700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854898286","data":{"timestamp":" 947854898285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854899344","data":{"timestamp":" 947854899343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854901177","data":{"timestamp":" 947854901177"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854901181","data":{"timestamp":" 947854901180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854902282","data":{"timestamp":" 947854902282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854904097","data":{"timestamp":" 947854904097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALINYANG"," userResponse":" PALINYANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854905766","data":{"timestamp":" 947854905765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854907292","data":{"timestamp":" 947854907292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854908972","data":{"timestamp":" 947854908972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854910999","data":{"timestamp":" 947854910998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854911094","data":{"timestamp":" 947854911094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854925053","data":{"timestamp":" 947854925053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 6fe5a917-e8c0-441e-9099-c9755f083b62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na hivyo ndivyo Palinyang' alianza kwenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854951010","data":{"timestamp":" 947854951010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 20395985-1186-4c95-a718-3b8c3670e130"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lazububu_zazumuba-lazububu-hasavefi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lazububu"," userResponse":" lazububu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854958914","data":{"timestamp":" 947854958913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 20395985-1186-4c95-a718-3b8c3670e130"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kosihife_heyiyiku-salitune-kosihife"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kosihife"," userResponse":" kosihife"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854963701","data":{"timestamp":" 947854963701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 20395985-1186-4c95-a718-3b8c3670e130"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_zazumuba_honojuye-lefarako-zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zazumuba"," userResponse":" honojuye"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854966927","data":{"timestamp":" 947854966926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 20395985-1186-4c95-a718-3b8c3670e130"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_zazumuba_honojuye-lefarako-zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947854986024","data":{"timestamp":" 947854986023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 20395985-1186-4c95-a718-3b8c3670e130"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.8.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_zazumuba_honojuye-lefarako-zazumuba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855006663","data":{"timestamp":" 947855006663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855007357","data":{"timestamp":" 947855007357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855007860","data":{"timestamp":" 947855007860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855008695","data":{"timestamp":" 947855008695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" JIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855009588","data":{"timestamp":" 947855009587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855009793","data":{"timestamp":" 947855009793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855010181","data":{"timestamp":" 947855010181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855010992","data":{"timestamp":" 947855010991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855013420","data":{"timestamp":" 947855013420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855020016","data":{"timestamp":" 947855020016"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855026262","data":{"timestamp":" 947855026262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855030929","data":{"timestamp":" 947855030929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855034812","data":{"timestamp":" 947855034811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855037769","data":{"timestamp":" 947855037768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855045035","data":{"timestamp":" 947855045035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855048331","data":{"timestamp":" 947855048331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855050011","data":{"timestamp":" 947855050010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855050907","data":{"timestamp":" 947855050907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855052800","data":{"timestamp":" 947855052799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855053548","data":{"timestamp":" 947855053547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855054357","data":{"timestamp":" 947855054356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855055081","data":{"timestamp":" 947855055081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855055580","data":{"timestamp":" 947855055580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855055808","data":{"timestamp":" 947855055807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855056270","data":{"timestamp":" 947855056270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855056648","data":{"timestamp":" 947855056648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855059203","data":{"timestamp":" 947855059202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855061225","data":{"timestamp":" 947855061225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855064223","data":{"timestamp":" 947855064223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855065907","data":{"timestamp":" 947855065906"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855067188","data":{"timestamp":" 947855067187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIISHI"," userResponse":" WALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855068786","data":{"timestamp":" 947855068786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855070433","data":{"timestamp":" 947855070433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855072201","data":{"timestamp":" 947855072200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855073587","data":{"timestamp":" 947855073587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855075503","data":{"timestamp":" 947855075503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855076942","data":{"timestamp":" 947855076941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855078415","data":{"timestamp":" 947855078414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855078427","data":{"timestamp":" 947855078426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855082638","data":{"timestamp":" 947855082638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" START_PAMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855086022","data":{"timestamp":" 947855086021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947855086151","data":{"timestamp":" 947855086150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000114_153717"," gameId":" 439862ef-4980-41ca-b5d2-efd6e92a0b30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" START_PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}